Karem Mahmoud AbdELkader

Full stack developer & instructor

Egiptian 🖪 30605011202458 🐞 Single 🜓 Waiting for the call 🔉 Male 🙋 Portofolio

EDUCATION

Graduate with distinction

We School of Applied Technology

I was studying the field of web and software development in addition to life skills and I graduated with distinction from the top ten in my specialty

10/2021 - 06/2024 Mansoura, Egypt

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MERN FULL STACK Developer

We school €

08/2023 - 09/2023 Mansoura, Egypt

THIS IS A VOLUNTEER SITE FOR MY SCHOOL AND IN IT I WAS ABLE TO APPLY WHAT I LEARNED IN THE FIELD OF MERN STACK

The site is a complete alternative to Google's Classroom site in addition to additional

https://we-school.vercel.app/

Front end developer

Zaman company &

07/2022 - 07/2022

Dubai, Uae I was working in a team on the development of this site and my job was frontend

HTML techniques used CSS JS and JS libararies tailwind CSS

This site is the site of home real estate trades in the UAE

LARAVEL FULL STACK DEVELOPER

We school

04/2024 - 04/2024Mansoura, Egypt

site "متبرع" It is a site to facilitate the process of blood donation that you developed in a competition International Youth Innovation

My project won the sixth place at the level of the Republic among 420 participating projects, which made me join the EdU TECH International Technology Exhibition

Freelancer Full_Stack developer

07/2023 - present Mansoura, Egypt

I have created many websites such as electronic stores, platforms for teachers and sites for private institutions, whether schools or companies, using MERN STACK and laravel

Instructor

06/2024 - present Dekernes, Egypt

To top Academy This is additional work besides my main work which is web development

I teach students the basics of programming, the field of the web, AI and robotics.

SKILLS

Time management Leadership

Frontend developer Team work

Back-end developer Ui developer

Microsoft office **Effective Communication**

Self-learning

PROFILE

As Full_Stack developer & instructor
I have the skill of developing effective websites
Whether the front or the back part
In addition, I have experience in electronic projects, whether for myself or for freelancer clients.
In addition to the teaching skill, I teach programming to children from 8 to 14 years old and young people from 16 to 30 years old.